威尔 · 森特斯: 托德，把它拿开，托德。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Todd,
take it away, Todd.
一号线，我们在干什么，我的朋友？
Line one, what are we doing,
my friend, here?
说话人2: 我们正在定义函数，复制，数组和除以二。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're defining the function,
copy, array and divide by two.
威尔 · 森特斯: 完美，顺便说一句，我做了最糟糕的事情。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Perfect, by the way,
I did the worst thing there.
你说话的时候我做对了，托德。
I did this right as you're talking, Todd.
我知道马克会为此感到多么沮丧。
I know how upset Mark will be by that.
定义函数，复制数组。
Define the function, copy array.
同志们，我们要再来一遍，因为我想让你们再次感受到
People, we're going to through it all over
again, because again, I want you to feel
从头再来一遍是多么令人沮丧。
in your guts how frustrating it
is to do this all over again.
这又是你从头开始写的代码。
This is code you're writing from scratch,
again.
你感受到了我的痛苦。
And you're feeling my pain of it.
这里没有拷贝和粘贴。
Ain't no copy and pasting here.
事实上，这是一个干净的白板过程。
In fact, it's a clean whiteboard process.
这就是重写代码的难度。
That's how hard it is to rewrite code.
当然，肯定有更好的办法，对吧？
Surely, there must be a better way, right?
当然，现在不行。
Surely, right now, no.
现在，不，它们在做不同的事情。
Right now, no,
these are doing different things.
函数代码是不同的。
The functions codes are different.
所以我们需要重新来过。
And so we need to do it all over again.
我的意思是只有一个字符不同，但它是不同的。
I means only one character different,
but it's different.
好了，托德，下一句。
All right, Todd, next line.
演讲者2: 它将定义常量 myarray。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It'll define
the constant myarray.
签上这个值。
Sign the value.
所以在1,2和3的数组中。
So in the array of 1, 2 and 3.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太美了。 谢谢你，托德。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful.
Thank you, Todd.
下一句，托德。
Next line, Todd.
演讲者2: 定义不变的结果
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Define
the constant result and
调用函数 copyArrayAndDivideBy2，传入1、2和3的参数。
call the function copyArrayAndDivideBy2,
passing in the argument of 1, 2, and 3.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 非常好，完全正确，调用函数 copyArray。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice, exactly,
call the function copyArray.
如果他不再回答同样的问题，除以2就是真的很糟糕,
Divide by 2 to be really bad if he
doesn't exactly same question again,
向右除以我的数组中的2部分123。
go right divided by 2 parts
in my array one two three.
顺便说一句，很不错,
Very nice by the way,
我们注意到那完整的技术交流有多好了吗？
do we notice how nice that complete
technical communication was?
我很清楚发生了什么。
I knew exactly what was happening.
谢谢你，托德。
Thank you, Todd.
好的，我们进入执行环境。
Okay, we go into the execution context.
没错没错。
Exactly, right.
我们把它放在那里，你把它放在调用堆栈上。
Let's put it on there you go
put it on the call stack.
各位，这是为了我们的长期观众。
People, this is for this is for
our long term audience.
他们喜欢我们完成的时候。
They love it when we complete.
2，it’ s
CompleteArrayAndDivideBy2, it's
全球动力总是在那别担心，丹。
being executed Global's always
there Don't worry, Dan.
还在那里，还在那里。
Also is there, there it is.
很好，让我们进入执行环境。
Excellent.
Let's go into the execution context.
而在当地的记忆里是什么第一凯拉？
And in local memory is what first Kayla?
说话人3: 我们用传入的值123来定义参数数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We define the parameter
array with the value passed in of 123.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, very nice.
哪一个是我们的？
Which is known as our?
说话人3: 一个参数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: A parameter.
那么一个参数是分配给我们的，每个人在一起？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So a parameter is
assigned our, everyone together?
讲者2: 论点 威尔 · 句子: 非常
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Argument.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Argument very
很好，非常好。
nice, excellent.
Kayla 非常感谢下一句 Kayla,
And Kayla thanks very much
on to the next line, Kayla,
我们在当地记忆里做的第一件事是什么？
what's the fist thing we
do in that local memory?
说话人3: 我们定义一个常量输出为空数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We define
a constant output to empty array.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太美了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful.
很好，让我们继续我们的迭代，通过我们的做循环
Excellent let's get moving on our
iteration our looping through our doing
一行代码作为 for 循环的主体。
a line of code the body of the for
loop multiple times.
好吗？
Okay?
还好，我们打到了身体的跟随。
There is all right,
we hit the body of follow.
眼睛的价值是什么，最初的泰勒？
Eyes value is what initially Taylor?
讲者3: Zero 威尔 · 森坦斯: 零，我们取数组
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Zero.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Zero we take array
定位 asub 或数组索引为零，然后得到值？
position or asub or
array index zero and get the value?
讲者3: 一 威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: One.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One.
我们把它除以2就得到了 Kayla？
We divide it by two, we get, Kayla?
演讲者3:0.5。
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: 0.5.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 0.5，或者用我们国家的话来说，每个人,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 0.5, or
as we say in my country, everybody,
也许你以前看过这些，我们说，也不是0.5，这是真的。
maybe you've watched this all before, we
say nor point five, which is a real thing.
尽管这听起来像是动态的东西。
Even though it sounds like
something from dynamic.
然后点击数组子，或数组索引，或数组位置1,
Then we hit array sub, or
array index, or array position one,
也就是我们除以2得到1的数字2。
which is the number two we
divide by two we get one.
好，我们去那里，它是1.5以及。
Okay, we go it there it is 1.5 as well.
很好，就是这个。
Good, there it is.
功能的最后一行，杰夫，说做什么？
Final line of the function,
Jeff, says to do what?
音箱2: 返回的输出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Returned output.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，我希望它能更精确一点，杰夫。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, I'd like it
to be more precise in that Jeff.
对我来说，输出是否表示标签或
Is it output which to me output represents
this whole combination of label or
但这并不是全部，不是吗？
identifier and value but
it's not the whole is it?
它只是-Speaker 2: 返回分配的值。
It's just the-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Return the value assigned.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, exactly.
非常好。
Very nice.
哪个。
Which.
这是数组0.51,1.5。
Which is the array 0.51, 1.5.
杰夫说得太好了。
Excellent from Jeff.
谢谢。这些数据存储在 global
Thank you.
And that's stored in global
在什么下面，杰夫。
under what constant Jeff.
讲者2: 结果如何？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Result?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 结果，太好了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Result.
Excellent.
好了。
There we go.
我们喜欢这个功能。
We love this function.
演讲者2: 从云霄飞车上跳下来。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Pop off the coaster.
威尔 · 森特斯: 再说一次，彼得，你必须把它从调用堆栈中取出来,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Again Peter,
you've got to pop it off the call stack,
他说对了。
he's spot on.
我们喜欢这个功能吗? 不，它的功能很好。
Do we like this function,
nah, his function is fine.
我们是否喜欢再次从头开始编写这个函数？
Do we like that we wrote this
function again from scratch?
每个人，谁知道[听不见]看这个，好吗。
Everybody, who knows
[INAUDIBLE] look at that, okay.
我们喜欢这个功能吗？
Do we like this function?
是的，他通常的功能，我们用这个任务很多,
Yes, his usual function we
use this with the task a lot,
但我真的需要从头开始重建吗？
but Did I really have to
rebuild it from scratch?
我想是的。
I guess I did though.
因为任何改变-我不能编辑功能，对不对？
Because any change- I can't
edit functions, right?
我救过他们一次也没有。
Not once I've saved them.
除非，在我们看到之前，让我们先看看另一个函数。
Unless- well, before we see,
let's for now see another function.
假设这次你想获取一个数组，创建一个全新的数组,
Suppose you wanted to take an array
this time, create a brand new array,
每个元素加上三个元素。
fill it with each element
with three added to it.
没错。
Yeah, exactly.
有趣的是，人们确实会轻微地呻吟，这是非常粗鲁的，托德。
It's funny people literally do groan
slightly, which is very rude, Todd.
那么，托德,
[LAUGH]
So, Todd,
你觉得我们违反了什么原则？
which principle are we
breaking here do you think?
演讲者2: 不干。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not dry.
威尔 · 森特斯: 它不是干的，我们有。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's not dry, we've got.
原则是不要重复你自己，我们正在重写。
The principle is don't repeat yourself,
we're rewriting.
每次我们这样做的时候，我们都会获得一个数组，创建一个新的输出数组
Every time we do this, we're taking
an array, creating a new output array
循环遍历输入数组，执行一些操作
iterating through the looping through
the input array, doing something
每个元素，返回完整的、完全填充的输出数组。
to each element, returning out of
the full, fully populated output array.
我们看到10的平方，9的平方，8的平方。
We saw that 10 squared,
nine squared, eight squared.
我们最终做得很好。
We in the end made it well.
我们做了一些事情来确保我们不必每次都重写
We did some things to make sure we
didn't have to rewrite each time
我们每次都能根据新数据进行调整。
we were able to adjust for
new data each time.
有人能告诉我我们在这里能做什么吗？
Can anybody tell me what could we do here?
不是像演讲中的一个华丽的标题词，而是
Not in terms of like a fancy
title word from the talk, but
没有更直观的感觉了。
there's no more intuitive sense.
也许，我们能做些什么来拯救我们自己，亚当？
What could we do to save ourselves Adam,
perhaps?
为了避免我们一个接一个地写出这些函数
To save ourselves from writing out
these functions one after another and
我们凭直觉能做些什么？
what can we do in a sort
of intuitive sense here?
演讲者2: 我们准备一个高阶函数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We teeing up for
a higher order function.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 好吧，我说了不要提到演讲的标题，丹,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, I said don't
mention the title of the talk [LAUGH] Dan,
说话人2: 传递功能为
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Pass functionality as
一个参数。
a parameter.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 丹说得很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautifully put by Dan.
是的，完全正确。
Yes, spot on.
我们可以留下一些功能。
We could leave some of our functionality.
我们可以写这些函数，把它留在空白处。
We could write these function ones,
leave it in a blank where the changes is.
我们不调用 copy123除以2,
We don't call this function copy123 and
divide it by 2,
copy123然后乘以2。
copy123 and multiply it by 2.
我们称之为 copyArray。
We call it copyArray.
然后当我们运行这个函数的时候，我们填充这个参数,
And then when we run the function,
we fill in that parameter,
使用特定的数据使该函数可重用。
With the specific data to
make that function reusable.
民谣，功能性也是一样。
Folk, same thing with functionality.
我们可以在特定的功能和
We can leave a little blank for
the specific functionality and
只有在我们运行函数之后才能填写。
only fill it in once we run the function.
但是我能这样做吗，各位？
But can I do it like this, people?
我能不能离开，我不知道,
Can I just leave, I don't know,
我可以插入 + 3吗，就像这样一个字符串。
can I just insert Plus three,
almost as a string like that.
我是否可以插入这个，然后把它送进去？
Am I allowed to insert that and
have that passed in?
我是否被允许传入一些小字符串的代码并在 JavaScript 中执行它们？
Am I allowed to pass in little strings
of code and execute them in JavaScript?
不。
Nah.
你可以想象一种语言。
You can imagine a language that would.
这并不是说你不能。
It's not saying you can't.
它不是固有的，但不是在 JavaScript 中。
It's not inherently,
but not in JavaScript.
那么，我们应该如何总结功能呢？
So instead,
how do we wrap up functionality?
将功能捆绑起来，这样它就可以执行了
Bundle up functionality,
such that it can execute Such as it can be
然后在另一个函数中运行,
passed through into and be then
executed run inside another function,
我们如何包装用 JavaScript 传递的功能代码？
how can we wrap up functionality code
to be passed around in JavaScript?
布莱登，我们怎么收尾，怎么收尾？
Braden, how can we wrap it up,
wrap it up with?
讲者2: 功能 威尔 · 森塔斯: 在一个功能中，他是点
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In function.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In a function he's spot
这正是我们要做的，我们可以泛化函数,
on and that's exactly what we're gonna do,
we could generalize our function,
我们称之为版权，做点什么吧。
let's call it copyright and do something.
复制数组和操作，看看这个。
Copy array and
manipulate and look at this.
我留下了一些空白指令，就像数组一样。
I've left a little blank instructions and
just as array.
只要你看到数组在版权范围内，除以2,
Wherever you saw array inside
of copyright and divide by two,
实际上变成了123。
it literally became 123.
我们会看到说明书会被填满
We're gonna see that instructions
is literally gonna be filled in
乘以二。
with Multiply by two.
看看这个。
Have a look at that.
我们有乘以二的函数，现在我把它保持在一条线上
We've got multiply by two function,
now I've kept it on one line but
这和正常的功能没什么不同。
it's no different to a normal function.
如果跑步得到了数字3，那么它会变成3乘2吗？
If run takes the number three,
will it turn out three by two?
我们乘以2，然后一行一行地走,
We pass in multiply by two, we're
gonna walk through this line by line,
大家别担心。
don't worry people.
但是它会逐渐取代指令这个词
But it's literally gonna replace
the word instructions there
复制数组操作保存声明定义代码,
inside of copy array manipulate
Save declare define the code,
当我们运行的时候它会替换它，代码会填充指令
it's going to replace it when we run that
code is going to fill in instructions
乘以二。
with, multiply by two.
然后看，乘以两个父母。
And then look, multiply by two parenths.
然后一个重新定位的零可以是数字1，乘以二人1。
And then a reposition zeros can be the
number one, multiply by two persons one.
也就是说，运行，乘以2，输入1和
That's to say run,
multiply by two With the input of 1 and
返回1乘2返回2和
return out 1 by 2 return out 2 and
我们的指令数组 i 将成为乘以2数组位置0。
our instructions array I which will
become multiply by 2 array position 0.
也就是说数字1的倍数乘以2的括号
That is to say the number 1
multiple by 2 parentheses 1 will
返回2和2将被推。
return out 2 and that 2 will be pushed.
进入输出。
Into output.
我们要做的和我们在这里做的一样，数组位置为零
We're gonna achieve exactly the same thing
we did here where array position zero with
一号，乘以二，但是
a number one, multiply by two, but
现在我们重新定位0是一个数字，并且
now we do a reposition
zero is a number one, and
然后我们把它插入乘以二，然后在它们返回的内部做一个个乘以二。
then we stick it into multiply by two and
do one by two inside their return out.
两个输入到输出。
The two inputs to output.